# Cyril Alvarez Adriaansen

Cryptocurrency Specialist | Execution/Sales Trader Full-stack Javascript Developer | BlockChain Developer

+34 653 895 269 (



me@cyril.page



Cvril.page



<u>Cyril-al-adriaansen</u> in



#### SKILLS

Business Development
Cryptocurrency Specialist
BlockChain Development
Trade Positioning
Technical Analysis
Hedge Funds Strategies
Programming

# EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF OXFORD Fintech Program 2018

UNIVERSITY OF MONTREAL Bachelor of Political Science Candidate 2002 - 2004

# CERTIFICATIONS

Chartered Institute for Securities & Investment (CISI)

IronHack, Full-stack JavaScript

Certified Bitcoin Professional (CBP)

Certified Blockchain Developer (CBD)

Certified Solidity Developer (CSD)

Certified Smart Contract Developer (CSCD)

#### **PROFILE**

Dynamic, accomplished Trading & Developer Professional highly regarded for 15+ years of progressive experience in driving equity and cryptocurrency trading/sales and blockchain efforts. Respected as a motivational, influential leader and collaborator who uses technical expertise to understand markets and trading positions, ensuring profitability. Out-of-the-box thinker committed to making continuous improvements in business development, risk management, and trading/market analysis to enable growth.

#### EXPERIENCE

# HEAD OF TRADING & BLOCKCHAIN 2gether | Madrid | 2017 - Present

- Deliver critical strategic and tactical insights as a member of the Steering Committee.
- Provide crucial advice across the organization on Blockchain, Cryptocurrency, Fintech & Decentralised Finance (DeFi).
- Demonstrate exceptional technical acumen in designing the Trading & Blockchain architecture.
- Build pre-ICO and ICO Smart contracts in Solidity, ensuring attainment of short and long-term goals.
- Helmed initiative for the Initial Coin Offering (ICO), and authored a subsequent handbook to convey best practices and common issues during the effort.

### CRYPTO CONSULTANT / DEVELOPER

Independent | Geneva, London, Madrid | 2013 - Present

- Incorporate data-driven assessments in investing in a wide array of cryptocurrencies, and act as an ICO Advisor.
- Expand expertise at every opportunity with all aspects of arbitrage and day trading
- Focus on improving forecasting and trend assessments.

# SALES/EXECUTION TRADER, Managing Director

Castle Harbour Securities | Geneva, London, Bermuda | 2011 - 2013

- Exceeded annual commission quota by 15%, handling equity, bond, and forex trade execution via DMA, algorithms, dark pools, and brokers while collaborating with cross-functional employees.
- Advised/identified appropriate investments and managed capital exposure as a trusted expert with risk management principles; noted as essential to a 20% upturn in overall company growth.
- Handled extensive market information, research, and news to organize sales efforts and improve trading.
- Achieved optimal trade execution by forging productive, professional relationships with multiple stakeholders, excelling as the primary liaison with technical trading questions.
- Provided clients with a wide array of input to improve their portfolio and exceed expectations.

# Cyril Alvarez Adriaansen

Cryptocurrency Specialist | Execution/Sales Trader Full-stack Javascript Developer | BlockChain Developer

+34 653 895 269 (



info@cyril.page



Cyril.page



Cyril-al-adriaansen in



### **VCard**



# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Linux

Github

**Smart Contracts** 

Google App Script

Javascript (MERN)

Python

HTML & CSS

# INTERESTS

Fintech

Artificial Intelligence

Solar Energy

Geopolitics

History

Traveling

Formula One

#### **EXPERIENCE** continued

SALES/EXECUTION TRADER, Vice President BTIG LTD. | London | 2009 - 2011

- Revised investment history and incorporated technical and fundamental analysis to establish trading positions.
- Analyzed strategic risk assessment strategies to maximize portfolio performance and minimize downside exposure consistently, building out subsequent standard operating procedures used across the entire organization.
- Drove strict and continuous regulatory compliance, and oversaw financial and technical analysis to determine lucrative trading situations, boosting profits by up to 10% despite volatile market conditions.
- Maintained comprehensives record of clients and fostered continued workflow
- Provided periodic feedback to clients and gained trust as a dedicated and capable resource.

TRADE SUPPORT, Associate

Jabre Capital | Geneva | 2007 - 2009.

- Supported 5 portfolio managers with \$4B under management in various funds; performed extensive research on new systems and technologies to improve market assessments and other data-heavy decisions.
- Maintained transactions in a wide array of systems, coordinating with a team of 30.
- Built tailored reports on convertible bonds, equity, options, and more while focusing on positive business impacts.
- Identified efficiency improvements to increase year-over-year profits.

Additional Experience: Trainee Derivatives Advisor, Bank Pictet & Cie, 2006

Languages: French, English, Spanish

# REFERENCES

Salvador Casquero 2gether | Founder +34 687 88 08 22



Omar Ulrich Castle harbour | CEO +41 79 859 54 00



Gary Hayes BTIG LTD. | Former CEO +44 20 7663 1700



Daniel Horsley
Anavio Capital | Founder
+44 78 1844 4100

